Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nguyen-huy-hoang-bryan (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

NoSQL

Microsoft SQL Server

Python

Nguyen Huy Hoang

Project Manager
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

Final-year software engineering student, aspiring software developer, with one-year experience teaching various programming languages. My ambition is to leverage technology and AI to revolutionize the traditional methods of software development.

: Java, Python, T-SQL, NoSQL, Microsoft Office, Bilingual (Vietnamese, English)

:

- Clothing store management app with Java
- H&K Clothing store management app with Java (RMI)
- Analysis of the play of the teams participating in EURO 2020
- Investigating NetFlix Movies Project
- Mentor of IV Quarter 2023 at MindX Technology
- 2nd of the MindX robot programming contest
- 3rd VietAnh International School Robot Programming Contest

I'm excited about new opportunities and challenges where I can learn about software.

I enjoy connecting with new people and hearing new perspectives, you can reach me at huyhoang.ng203@gmail.com.

Experience

SG HONG PHAT
Assistant Project Manager
November 2024 - Present (5 months)

SEA EDU Assistant Manager June 2024 - Present (10 months) MindX Technology School Robotics Teacher June 2023 - Present (1 year 10 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

ICanTech VN
Python Teacher
June 2022 - January 2024 (1 year 8 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Education

Industrial University of Ho Chi Minh City

Bachelor's degree, Computer Software Engineering · (August 2021)